Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Greenwich mill workers given wage increase, more holidays, 1949-1954 (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Violence threads long paper strike, 1949-1954 (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Protest 'short time' work schedule here, 1949-1954 (Box 295, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Public observance of fifteen years of progress and burning of the mortgage, 1948; Publication (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Paper makers in Canada: a history of the Paper Makers Union in Canada, 1952; Publication (Box 295, Folder 2)
    Author: William E. Greening
  - Item 3: Addresses of J. T. Carey and J. J. O'Connor of the Paper Makers Union, Stuart Reid of the American Federation of Labor, 1908; Publication (Box 295, Folder 2)
    Author: J. T. Carey; J. J. O'Connor; Stuart Reid
  - Item 4: Compilation of data: existing union contracts, organized mills, unorganized mills, grades of paper, 1939; Publication (Box 295, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, Publication (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Statements of policy relating to the 1946-1947 Uniform Labor Agreement, Publication (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: It's your union now!, Publication (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Joint Labor and Management Safety Conference, Publication (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Statements of policy taken from the record of negotiations, 1945; Publication (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: A review of the Report of the Research CommitteeLabor unrest and dissaftisfaction, 1944; Publication (Box 295, Folder 3)
    Author: Frances Perkins
  - Item 6: Labor relations by Bart L. Tidland to the 1947 Convention of the American Pulp and Paper Mill Superintendents Assoc., Publication (Box 295, Folder 3)
    Author: Bart L. Tidland
  - Item 7: Labor unrest and dissatisfaction: report of the study made by the special research committee, 1944; Publication (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Little Korea--USA., 1955; Publication (Box 295, Folder 3)
    Author: Thomas Sancton
- United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: handwritten - Quarterly report, 1900; Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Outline of six-week course for District 6, UPWA-CIO, 1953; Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: 1969 Economic and Collective Bargaining Report, Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The good old days; Remember?, Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Control, Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Your Secret Weapon, Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Join and support the Union that supports you, Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The 'Do it yourself' idea is great but, Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Organization your road to New Frontiers on your job, Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Follow you own good judgment (sic), Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Times have changed, Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: correspondence, 1972; Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Colunteer Organizers manual, 1961; Publication (Box 295, Folder 4)
- United Paperworkers of America. (UPA), Publication (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Journal - vol. 1, no. 1-2, 1957; Publication (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Retirement plan, 1949; Publication (Box 295, Folder 5)
    Author: Gardner Board and Carton Co.
  - Item 3: Successful grievance handling: a manual for UPA-CIO shop stewards, Publication (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: For UPA-CIO Stewards and Committeemen, 1949; Publication (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Local 414 "Spotlight", 1951-1952 (Box 295, Folder 5)
- United Paperworkers of America. (UPA), Publication (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Officers report - (1st ) Constitutional Conventions, 1948; Publication (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Security and jobs for all in our home town!, 1946; Publication (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Parliamentary Law Chart, 1946; Publication (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: For job security!, For better wages, 1946; Publication (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Auditor's report, 1952; Publication (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: The Continental Story, 1950; Publication (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Courier, 1953; Publication (Box 295, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 5, issue 24-28
  - Item 8: Labor peace hope blasted by strike, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Strikers shut off auxiliary plant, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: To sue paper concern, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Clash is averted at Jersey strike, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Police on the alert for strike violence, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Company refuses to recognize union, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Paper head assailed, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Arson laid to 2 strikers, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Plan to reopen mill is rejected by union, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Strike leader guilty, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Labor pact to lift paper-making costs, 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Paper firm in NJ reopens after union agrees to unusual..., 1949-1950 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Car is demolished in Jersey strike, 1950-1954 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Unions receive 5-cent increase, 1950-1954 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: CIO union restrained in paper plant strike, 1950-1954 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: Bloomer firm, union agree on new wage, vacation plan, 1950-1954 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 24: Right-wing union challenges UOPWA, 1950-1954 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 25: Jersey paper plant strike ended..., 1950-1954 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Item 26: Paper mill closed by 7-month strike, 1950-1954 (Box 295, Folder 6)
- United Paperworkers of America. (UPA), Publication (Box 295, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: UPA-CIO Local 1208 News, 1953; Publication (Box 295, Folder 7)
    Notes: Apr., June (1953)
  - Item 2: News and Views, 1953; Publication (Box 295, Folder 7)
    Notes: Feb. (1953)
- United Paperworkers of America. (UPA), Publication (Box 295, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Our news, 1954; Publication (Box 295, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 8-10
- United Paperworkers of America. (UPA), Publication (Box 295, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Local 414 "Spotlight", 1952-1953 (Box 295, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: The Union position on job evaluation, 1948; Publication (Box 295, Folder 9)
- United Paperworkers International Union, Publication (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Strike policy handbook, 1973; Publication (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Plan to live all your life: a handbook for retirement planning, 1969; Publication (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Roll Call of Delegates to the first convention, 1976; Publication (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Schedule of special events - First Convention, 1976; Publication (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Permanent Committees of the Third Constitutional convention, 1984; Publication (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Press Release, 1982; Publication (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: 1982 Issues facing Congress, Publication (Box 295, Folder 10)
- United Paperworkers International Union, Publication (Box 295, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Resolutions presented to the (First, Second) Convention., 1976-1980 (Box 295, Folder 11)
- Independent Petroleum Workers Union, Publication (Box 297, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A history of the Independent Petroleum Workers Union, Albany, New York, 1971; Publication (Box 297, Folder 1)
    Author: Bruce Crate
- Independent Petroleum Workers Union, Publication (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: IUPW Newsletter - 1961; Oct., Dec. (1960), 1960-1961 (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Free Labour World, 1960; Publication (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Look before you leap, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: No Contribution, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 2)
- Philadelphia Labor Institute, Publication (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Dedication Souvenir 1926, Publication (Box 297, Folder 3)
    Author: Philadelphia Labor Institute
  - Item 2: 19 study classes were started by the Labor College of Philadelphia during the 1926-27 season, 1927; Publication (Box 297, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Conference on Textiles as a community problem, 1929; Publication (Box 297, Folder 3)
- A. Philip Randolph Institute, Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Current biography - Randloph, A(SA) Philip (1951), Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: A. Philip Randolph: Labor's Grand Old Man, 1969; Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
    Notes: Reprinted from May, 1969 Ebony. 2 copies
  - Item 3: Catalyst: The A. Philip Randolph Institute sparks a 'political' attack on slums and poverty, Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: "Black Power" and coalition politics, 1966; Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
    Author: Bayard Rustin
  - Item 5: Race, rage and Eldridge Cleaver, 1968; Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
    Author: Jervis Anderson
    Notes: Reprinted from Commentary, December 1968
  - Item 6: The A. Philip Randolph Institute: Agent for change, Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Education in a changing society, 1968; Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The lessons of the long hot summer, 1967; Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: correspondence, 1969; Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: TULC-MDLCA, A. Philip Randolph Freedom House, 1968; Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
    Author: A. Philip Randolph Freedom House
  - Item 11: Repeal 14B, 1968-1970 (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: A. Philip Randolph Education Fund Annual report, 1968-1969 (Box 297, Folder 4)
    Author: A. Philip Randolph Education Fund
  - Item 13: A. Philip Randolph Education Fund Annual report, 1969-1970 (Box 297, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: A "freedom budget" for all Americans; budgeting our resources, 1966-1975, to achieve "freedom from want", Publication (Box 297, Folder 4)
    Author: A. Philip Randolph Institute
- A. Philip Randolph Institute, Publication (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A. Philip Randolph at 80: tributes and recollections, 1969; Publication (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: A "freedom budget" for all Americans: a summary, 1967; Publication (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Conflict or coatlition?: the civil rights struggle and the trade union movement today, 1969; Publication (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Three essays, 1969; Publication (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Which Way Out?: A Way out of the Exploding Ghetto, 1969; Publication (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Right to work laws, a trap for America's minorities, 1968; Publication (Box 297, Folder 5)
- International Photo-Engravers' Union of North America, Publication (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Basic Economic Data manual, 1954; Publication (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Official Label Directory, 1946; Publication (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: President's Report to Forty-fourth - Annual Meeting, 1958; Publication (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Pension-Welfare Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Reports of Officers and Representatives of the, 1945; Publication (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: National apprenticeship standards [for] photo engravers [in the] newspaper publishing business, 1948; Publication (Box 297, Folder 6)
- American Pilots Association, Publication (Box 297, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Trade unionists or Strikebreakers?, 1927; Publication (Box 297, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: American Pilots Association - Memo, 1956; Publication (Box 297, Folder 7)
- International Photo-Engravers' Union of North America, Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Engravers' strike curtails printing of Dailies in City, 1953-1954 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Union to study under mediator, 1953-1954 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Printing resumed by Herald Tribune strike talks go on, 1953-1954 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Piano workers sign 2-Year contract, 1953-1954 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Union arranges grievance study, 1953-1954 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Picket lines and contracts, 1953-1954 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Engravers agree to $3.75 pay rise, 1953-1954 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: News labor issue coming up today, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Matthew Woll dies at age of 76, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: LI paper is eighth to close in strike, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: City's newspapers resume publication, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Who wins a strike?, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Photo-engravers get $3.75 award, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Engravers' Pay plan rejected by publisher, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Union meeting called in news strike, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: The disruption, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Fact finders may be called by engravers, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Engravers refuse to halt strike, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Tribune shutdown leaves New Yorkers paperless, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: New Yorkers annoyed and news-ad-hungry, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: espaper strike shows 'it pays to advertise', 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: Another paper halts publication in New York, 1953; Publication (Box 297, Folder 8)
- Operative Plasterers and Cement Mansons. International Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Nature of the work, 1979; Publication (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Group insurance plan (Brooklyn Plasterers Insurance Fund), 1946; Publication (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Circular Letter no. 57, 1976; Publication (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: National apprenticeship standards for cement masonry, asphalt, and composition trade, 1976; Publication (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: National standards for cement, asphalt, and composition finishing apprenticeship ..., 1947; Publication (Box 298, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The 314 Plastering Industry Pension Fund presents Your Pension Program, 1954; Publication (Box 298, Folder 1)
- Operative Plasterers and Cement Mansons. International Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, 1950-1951 (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Circular Letter no. 45, 1972; Publication (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Job opportunities in the concrete industries, Publication (Box 298, Folder 2)
- International Steel and Copper Plate printers' Union of North America, Publication (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Plate Printer, 1913; Publication (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Upson, Union to announce terms Monday, 1952-1954 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: CIO Union withdraws election petition for Coro's RI Plant, 1952-1954 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: New agreement ratified by Upson Employees, 1952-1954 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Toy Company signs pact on GM's pattern, 1952-1954 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Dispute over, 1952-1954 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Upson help back on jobs, 1952-1954 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Ousted union seeks readmission to CIO, 1952-1954 (Box 298, Folder 3)
- United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, Publication (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Stand by the Plumbers' Helpers, Publication (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: ReportLabor Education in your local union, 1905; Publication (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: AFL Plumbers' report on health & welfare plans, 1955; Publication (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The National Plumbing Apprenticeship Plan, Publication (Box 298, Folder 5)
    Notes: brittle, with no cover, front or back
  - Item 5: Twenty-Fourth Annual convention proceedings, 1928; Publication (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Report of the actuary on the proposed pension plan, 1948; Publication (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Trust fund, 1952; Publication (Box 298, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: An analysis of our AFL-CIO role in Latin America: or, Under the covers with the CIA., 1974; Publication (Box 298, Folder 5)
- United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, Publication (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1947; Publication (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: 100 Years of Excellence (souvenir booklet), 1990; Publication (Box 299, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: 100th Anniversary 1890-1990 (souvenir booklet), Publication (Box 299, Folder 1)
- International Harvester; United Association of Journeymen, Plumbers and Steamfitters, Pipefitters. Local 522, Publication (Box 299, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Arbitration Award, Publication (Box 299, Folder 2)
    Author: International Harvester; United Association of Journeymen, Plumbers and Steamfitters, Pipefitters. Local 522
  - Item 2: Program - Testimonial Dinner honoring Mr. George Meany, 1952; Publication (Box 299, Folder 2)
- United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, Publication (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Recommendations and report, Publication (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: A short history of the worshipful company of plumbers, 1955; Publication (Box 299, Folder 3)
    Author: William Champness
  - Item 3: Explanation of hiring practices necessary under the Taft-Hartley Act, October 24, 1958., Publication (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Pipe trades trust fund, 1952; Publication (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Health and Welfare Plan of the Peninsula Plumbing Industry Trust Fund, 1952; Publication (Box 299, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Benefits provided by the welfare fund, 1949; Publication (Box 299, Folder 3)
- United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, Publication (Box 299, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: General Officers' Weekly Newsletter - vol. XVIII, no. 1-2,4, 1972; Publication (Box 299, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Facing the craft challenges of tomorrow, 1965; Publication (Box 299, Folder 4)
- Fancy Leather-Goods Worker, Publication (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Recommendations and report, 1955; Publication (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: To all loyal members of the Int. Pocketbook Workers Union, Publication (Box 299, Folder 5)
    Language: English;Yiddish.
  - Item 3: Statement by the Joint Board of the Int. Pocketbook Workers Union, Publication (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Election Number!, 1928; Publication (Box 299, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 2
  - Item 5: A General Strike, Publication (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Report from the General President - Labor Eduation in your local union, 1955; Publication (Box 299, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Recommendations and report, Publication (Box 299, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters (BSCP), Publication (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 3 Handbag locals sue to avoid unity, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Bag workers press demand for $4 raise, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: New contract terms ratified by bag union, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Talks starting today on new handbag pact, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: handbag labor pact extended one week, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Facing fourth bad season, union asks relief from tax, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: 12-1/2 an hour pay rise asked by bag union, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Union official cites figures showing industry progress, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Pocketbook workers Union celebrates 30 years' existence, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Press Release, 1963; Publication (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: 8.5 % pay rise is awarded to bag workers, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Union brief urges excise tas repeal, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Anti- US import move by Canadian labor is deplored, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Union official anticipates successful fall season, 1948-1951 (Box 299, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters (BSCP), Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A message from the Governor of Oregon, Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: The Social Service Bulletin, 1927; Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
    Author: Methodist Federation for Social Service
    Notes: vol. 17, no. 7. 2 copies
  - Item 3: The Pullman Porters' Struggle, 1928; Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
    Author: Boston Citizens' Committee
  - Item 4: Sleeping Car Porters will 'go all the way' to win 40-hour week, 'overdue' wage increase and job security, 1963; Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: correspondence, 1927-1936 (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: New York Leading Negro Ministers endorse Pullman Porters Union, Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Pullman Porters Organize Union, 1927; Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
    Author: National Catholic Welfare Conference
  - Item 8: Bulletin, Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 23
  - Item 9: Concerning - New York Citizens Committee of one hundred in behalf of Pullman Porters, Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Negro changes his attitude toward the trade unions, 1927; Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
    Author: John J. Leary
  - Item 11: Marching song of the BSCP, Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Bulletin - A call to Pullman Porters for action, Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: invitation to - Theatre Party-Lafayette Theatre, 1936; Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Bulletin - Pass this bulletin on the a Porter, Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: An appeal to you for help, Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Fifteenth Anniversary and Bi-Ennial ConventionSouvenir journal, 1940; Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: The Pullman porter, 1926; Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: The Pullman porter, 1927; Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: World of a pullman porter, Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
    Author: Douglas Taylor
  - Item 20: Before the Interstate Commerce Commission, Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters against the Pullman Company, Publication (Box 299, Folder 7)
- National Federation of Post Office Clerks, Publication (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: correspondence, 1960; Publication (Box 300, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The Cincinnati FED, 1952; Publication (Box 300, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 11, no. 4
  - Item 3: The Cincinnati FED, 1952; Publication (Box 300, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 12, no. 2, 4-6
  - Item 4: The Cincinnati FED, 1953; Publication (Box 300, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 13, no. 3
- National Federation of Post Office Clerks, Publication (Box 300, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Cincinnati FED, 1953; Publication (Box 300, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 13, no. 2, 4-8
  - Item 2: The Cincinnati FED, 1953; Publication (Box 300, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 14, no. 9-10
  - Item 3: The Cincinnati FED, 1954; Publication (Box 300, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 15, no. 1, 6
  - Item 4: The Cincinnati FED, 1954-1955 (Box 300, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 16, no. 1-4, 6, 8-10
- National Federation of Post Office Clerks, Publication (Box 300, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Cincinnati FED, 1956; Publication (Box 300, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 17, no. 1-8, 11
  - Item 2: The Cincinnati FED, 1957; Publication (Box 300, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 18, no. 1-2, 4-5, 8- 9
  - Item 3: The Cincinnati FED, 1958; Publication (Box 300, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 19, no. 2- 7